## **Thomas**

# Vanderhaeghen

Freelance developer and coach php, react and devops

### Contact

Parklaan 60, 9000 Gent +32 472 48 45 30 info@vdh.gent

## **Summary**

My name is Thomas Vanderhaeghen and specialise in PHP development. In my 11 years as a professional developer I also picked up skills in React (typescript), devops and project management.

I believe that alone or together with your team my experience and skill can make a difference in your company.

While developing help is always welcome, either building a good foundation for new applications or improving on already existing applications. Either way I will work hard to set you up for success.

### **Skills**

PHP / Symfony	
React / typescript / javascript	
Sql	
Redis	
Elastic	
AWS DevOps	
Kubernetes / Docker	
HTML & CSS	
Agile Project Management	
Leadership and Teamwork	
Customer Relations	

## Work experience

### Start as freelance developer

2023 - ...



### **Optios**

Lead Developer 2017 – 2022, Lochristi All-in-one software voor kappers en schoonheidssalons PHP, AWS, MySQL, React, elastic, redis, docker, kubernetes, Project mangement, team lead



### Diligentia uitgeverij

PHP Developer 2014 – 2016, Wondelgem Schoolbeheer en interactief platform PHP (Symfony 2), MySQL, Angular.js, lead developer



#### iController

PHP Developer 2013 – 2014, Lokeren Debiteuren beheer PHP, MySQL, Puppet, Product owner



#### aware

PHP Developer 2012 – 2013, Gent Applicaties ter ondersteuning van een workflow binnen een bedrijf PHP (Symfony 1, 2), Perl, MySQL

## Languages

### **Education**

Nederlands

----

KAH Sint-Lievens Sep 2007 – Jun 2011, Gent Professionele Bachelor ICT

Français

English

Visitatie Mariakerke, Informatica Sep 2004 – Jun 2006, Mariakerke Middelbaar

Italiano

#### VISO

Sep 2002 – Jun 2004, Mariakerke Grafische vormgeving, Middelbaar